{
  "name": "",
  "isFavorite": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Happy",
      "back": "Mutlu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sad",
      "back": "Üzgün"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Angry",
      "back": "Kızgın"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Tired",
      "back": "Yorgun"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Excited",
      "back": "Heyecanlı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Scared",
      "back": "Korkmuş"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Worried",
      "back": "Endişeli"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Surprised",
      "back": "Şaşırmış"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Lonely",
      "back": "Yalnız"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Calm",
      "back": "Sakin"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Confused",
      "back": "Kafası karışık"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Shy",
      "back": "Utanmış"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Embarrassed",
      "back": "Mahcup"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Proud",
      "back": "Gururlu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Bored",
      "back": "Sıkılmış"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Jealous",
      "back": "Kıskanç"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Relaxed",
      "back": "Rahatlamış"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Nervous",
      "back": "Gergin"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hopeful",
      "back": "Umutlu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Grateful",
      "back": "Minnettar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cheerful",
      "back": "Neşeli"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Anxious",
      "back": "Endişeli"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Furious",
      "back": "Öfkeli"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Disappointed",
      "back": "Hayal kırıklığına uğramış"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hopeful",
      "back": "Umutlu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Upset",
      "back": "Üzgün, canı sıkkın"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Friendly",
      "back": "Arkadaş canlısı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Brave",
      "back": "Cesur"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Kind",
      "back": "Nazik"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Mean",
      "back": "Kaba, huysuz"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Polite",
      "back": "Kibar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Rude",
      "back": "Kaba"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Lazy",
      "back": "Tembel"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Active",
      "back": "Aktif"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Energetic",
      "back": "Enerjik"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Curious",
      "back": "Meraklı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Silly",
      "back": "Aptalca, saçma"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Smart",
      "back": "Zeki"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Serious",
      "back": "Ciddi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Friendly",
      "back": "Dost canlısı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Moody",
      "back": "Karamsar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Charming",
      "back": "Çekici"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Gentle",
      "back": "Nazik, yumuşak"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Clumsy",
      "back": "Sakar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Talkative",
      "back": "Konuşkan"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Quiet",
      "back": "Sessiz"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Funny",
      "back": "Komik"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Helpful",
      "back": "Yardımsever"
    }
  ]
}
